LE VU

+84765860900 · cody.ellington.lee@gmail.com · portfolio.codyellingtonlee.com Go Vap, Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

TECHNICAL RESEARCH & DEVELOPMENT SPECIALIST

Hi, my name is Vu, or you can call me Cody. As a Technical R&D professional, I specialize in pushing technological boundaries through research and innovation. With a passion for staying ahead of emerging trends, I excel in analyzing data and implementing solutions across diverse industries. My collaborative mindset and commitment to excellence drive impactful results in R&D projects.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

H&N Investment Consultancy IT Intern

March 2021 - June 2021

- Optimize SEO and Page Speed Insight score for all company website.
- Handle technical social media problem.
- · Research social media algorithm for bossting the organic traffic

H&N Investment Consultancy

June 2021 - November 2021

- Contract Freelancer
 - Use Webflow to develop and maintain website (delements.co).
 - Develop a keyword filter and insight website for Marketing Team.
 - Build up social media clone account system by using VPS and some Black-hat SEO tools.
 - Help Finance Team to optimize Google Sheet formular and add some automation by using Google App Script.
- Gather and categorize insight data from social media and adjust the strategy with Marketing Team.

H&N Investment Consultancy IT Specialist cum Administrator & System

November 2021 - Present

- Full-stack develop an E-commerce fashion website (rootrotation.com) by using Shopify platform.
 - Research and work with Finance Team to intergrate paygate to Shopify.
 - Research and implement effeciency plugin and app to boost up the website.
 - Use HTML, CSS and JS to optimize website custom structure through Shopify liquid files.
 - Develope a sub-site by using Webflow and jQuery (artwear.rootrotation.com)
- Develope micro site about gaming using Phaser 3, Boostrap and Tailwinds framework.
- Research and implement AI Tools to reduce company's workload and push up the performance.
 - o Graphic / Designer Team: MidJourney, Stable Diff, Photoshop Al and Leonardo Al.
 - Music Team: Real-time Voice Changer, W-Okada, Manjio RVC.
 - o Marketing Team: GPTs, Gemini.
- Create immersive experience for Phygital Fashion (Augmented Reality)
- Prepare instruction documents about the workflow and how to use AI tools.
- Prepare and manage IT budget each month and organization's emails (G-Workspace, Slack)
- · Work with BA and HR to implement the Base ERP for fashion clothes production chain.
- Handle and maintain tech properties. (Laptop, Mobile Phone, Data Sim Card, Tracking Motion Suit)
- Work with Graphic Team and Production Team to create rigged character for animation.
- Take responsibility on technical of live streams (included 24/7 live streams) and its insight.
- Take part in dropshipping side-project of the company.

EDUCATION

Nong Lam University HCMC

Graduated Diploma in Information System

2021

HARD SKILLS

HTML / CSS / JS Bootstrap / Tailwinds Phaser jQuery SQL SEO (White & Black)

Edit Image and Video Git / Github Digital Marketing

SOFT SKILLS

Research and Implementation
Documentation
Strategic Planning

Financial Planning Negotiation Skills Client Relationship Management Team Leadership Communication Operations Management

TOOL / PLATFORM SKILLS

Shopify & Webflow MyWebAR Base ERP

Mid Journey Stable Diffusion LeonardoAl Photoshop Capcut Canva

Tensor Art W-Okada RVC Manjio RVC Base ERP Google Workspace Microsoft Office

> GPT Gemini Devin

CERTIFICATES

Digital Marketing

Google Digital Grarage

Software Development With Scrum

Axon Active

Responsive Web Design

freeCodeCamp

References are available on request.